<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Parcelable Demo</string>
  <string name="temples">Temples</string>
  <string name="location">Location</string>

  <string-array name="temple_titles">
    <item>Brihadisvara Temple</item>
    <item>Meenakshi Amman Temple</item>
    <item>Nataraja Temple</item>
    <item>Palani Murugan temple</item>
    <item>Kanchi Kailasanathar Temple</item>
    <item>Annamalaiyar Temple</item>
    <item>Ramanathaswamy Temple</item>
    <item>Thiruchendur Murugan temple</item>
    <item>Ekambareswarar Temple</item>
    <item>Saleth Matha Church</item>
    <item>Gorippalayam Dargah</item>
  </string-array>
  <string-array name="temple_desc">
    <item>Brihadishvara Temple, also referred to as Rajesvara Peruvudaiyar or Brihadeeswarar Temple, is a Hindu temple dedicated to Shiva located in Thanjavur, Tamil Nadu, India</item>
    <item>Meenakshi Temple, also referred to as Meenakshi Amman or Minakshi-Sundareshwara Temple, is a historic Hindu temple located on the southern bank of the Vaigai River
      in the temple city of Madurai, Tamil Nadu, India. It is dedicated to Meenakshi, a form of Parvati, and her consort, Sundareswar, a form of Shiva.
      The temple is at the center of the ancient temple city of Madurai mentioned in the Tamil Sangam literature, with the goddess temple mentioned in 6th century CE texts</item>
    <item>The temple has mythical roots and a Shiva shrine existed at the site when the town was known as Thillai. Chidambaram, the name of the city and the temple
      literally means "atmosphere of wisdom" or "clothed in thought", the temple architecture symbolizes the connection between the arts and spirituality, creative activity
      and the divine. The temple wall carvings display all the 108 karanas from the Natya Shastra by Bharata Muni, and these postures form a foundation of Bharatanatyam,
      a classical Indian dance.</item>
    <item>Palani Arulmigu Shri Dhandayuthapani temple is one of the Six Abodes of Murugan. It is located in the town of Palani in Dindigul, 100 kilometres (62 mi) southeast of
      Coimbatore and northwest of Madurai in the foot-hills of the Palani hills, Tamil Nadu, India. Palani temple is considered synonymous with Panchamirtam,
      a sweet mixture made of five ingredients.</item>
    <item>The kanchi Kailasanathar temple is the oldest structure in Kanchipuram. Located in Tamil Nadu, India, it is a Hindu temple in the Dravidian architectural style.
      It is dedicated to the Lord Shiva, and is known for its historical importance.</item>
    <item>Annamalaiyar Temple is an Hindu temple dedicated to the deity Shiva, located at the base of Annamalai hills in the town of Thiruvannamalai in Tamil Nadu, India.
      It is significant to the Hindu sect of Saivism as one of the temples associated with the five elements, the Pancha Bhoota Stalas, and specifically the element of fire,
      or Agni. Shiva is worshiped as Annamalaiyar or Arunachaleswarar, and is represented by the lingam, with his idol referred to as Agni lingam.</item>
    <item>Ramanathaswamy Temple (இராமநாதஸ்வாமி கோயில் Irāmanātasvāmi Kōyil) is a Hindu temple dedicated to the god Shiva located on Rameswaram island in the state of Tamil Nadu,
      India. It is also one of the twelve Jyotirlinga temples. It is one of the 274 Paadal Petra Sthalams, where the three of the most revered Nayanars (Saivite saints), Appar,
      Sundarar and Tirugnana Sambandar, have glorified the temple with their songs. </item>
    <item>Thiruchendur Murugan temple is known as the second Arupadai Veedu of Lord Muruga. Lord Muruga won the battle with the asura, Surapadma and worshipped Lord Shiva
      in this sacred place. The temple is situated along the shores of the Bay of Bengal.T</item>
    <item>The temple is believed to have been existing since 600 AD but, the present structure is said to be dating back to 11th-12th centuries.
      The architecture of the temple showcases a signature Shaivite structure with a lofty gopuram, 5 prakrams or concentric circumambulatory enclosures.
      The 1000 pillared hall adorning carvings of 1008 Shivlingas is believed to be added by the Vijayanagara kings during 15th century.
      The inner sanctum houses the Prithvi Lingam. Also, the sacred mango tree, believed to be more than 3000 years old, can be seen in the temple premises.</item>
    <item>La Saleth Church or Saleth Matha Church is one of the popular churches of Kodaikanal about three kms from Kodaikanal bus stand. It is one of the oldest churches
      in the locality which is more than 130 years old. We took a long walk through Bryant Park to reach the church. The church is very colorful and is a great attraction for
      the localites as well as tourists. It was worth trekking all the way.</item>
    <item>Goripalayam Mosque is a large mosque in Goripalayam (part of Madurai City) containing two graves (tombs) of sultans of Yemen namely Hazrat Khaja Syed Sultan Alauddin Badusha
      razi and Hazrat Khaja Syed Sulthan Shamsuddin of the Madurai Sultanate.There is also one invisible grave of Hazrat Khaja Syed Sultan Habibuddin razi who is also known as
      Ghaibi Sultha who came to India to spread Islam.</item>
  </string-array>
  <string-array name="temple_address">
    <item>Membalam Rd, Balaganapathy Nagar, Thanjavur, Tamil Nadu 613007</item>
    <item>Madurai Main, Madurai, Tamil Nadu 625001</item>
    <item>Chidambaram, Tamil Nadu 608001</item>
    <item>Giri Veethi, Palani, Tamil Nadu 624601</item>
    <item>Pillaiyarpalayam, Kanchipuram, Tamil Nadu 631501</item>
    <item>Pavazhakundur, Tiruvannamalai, Tamil Nadu 606601</item>
    <item>Rameswaram, Tamil Nadu 623526</item>
    <item>Tiruchendur, Tamil Nadu</item>
    <item>Kanchipuram</item>
    <item>Kodaikanal, Tamil Nadu 624101</item>
    <item>On The Bank Of Vaigai River, Madurai, Tamil Nadu, 625001</item>
  </string-array>
</resources>
